<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Artikkelin Paracasin pidennetyt kallot paljastavat: ei mikään tunnettu eliölaji kommentit	</title>
	<atom:link href="/tiede/paracasin-pidennetyt-kallot-paljastavat-ei-mikaan-tunnettu-eliolaji/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tiede/paracasin-pidennetyt-kallot-paljastavat-ei-mikaan-tunnettu-eliolaji/</link>
	<description>Eksopolitiikka, UFOt, Paranormaalit ilmiöt, Tietoisuus</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 02:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		Kirjoittaja: J-Rod		</title>
		<link>/tiede/paracasin-pidennetyt-kallot-paljastavat-ei-mikaan-tunnettu-eliolaji/#comment-19836</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[J-Rod]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 02:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=650#comment-19836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sorry. I Meant the honourable Bolon Yokte&#039; K&#039;uh from the Braxszaallkh 7896 g 11 -dimension of the 11-zystemuz beyond the NOOA BUI2, but when copied the the name from your WIKIPEDIA, the DETVA  
( Draconian electric torus agents) changed the information, so that the message could´t get through to THE SOURCE.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sorry. I Meant the honourable Bolon Yokte&#8217; K&#8217;uh from the Braxszaallkh 7896 g 11 -dimension of the 11-zystemuz beyond the NOOA BUI2, but when copied the the name from your WIKIPEDIA, the DETVA<br />
( Draconian electric torus agents) changed the information, so that the message could´t get through to THE SOURCE.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Kirjoittaja: J-Rod		</title>
		<link>/tiede/paracasin-pidennetyt-kallot-paljastavat-ei-mikaan-tunnettu-eliolaji/#comment-19835</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[J-Rod]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 01:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=650#comment-19835</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bolon Kokte K’uh and Akhenaten are related to these things. Have you ever wondered, why the ancient cultures have vanished? If you look the South America (Inkas, Mayans), Sumer (Irak and Iran) and Egypt etc. Everything is now fucked up, because the advanced  alien and human civilisations have left the Planet. The Atlantis sinked in the Bermuda Triangle, and that is the reason why the Illuminati controlled scientific community have mapped for instance the Moon better than the Ocean Floor.  Have you ever wondered the Kuiper Belt? Why the asteroids aren´t forming planets as they should be? It´s Because the planet MALDEK destroyed in the past. Illuminati, mainstream scientists and Vatican tell you lies, that the asteroids of the Kuiper Belt are leftovers after the formation of your solar system millions of years ago. Illuminati and Vatican controls your whole planet and keep the important things secret, so that they can manipulate and direct your destiny. Unfortunately the orders comes from much more higher seat. The hierarchy of the Universal Power is multidimensional and eternal and reaches beyond your Space Time Continuum. Unfortunately The Great Architect made a mistake in Your &quot;Big Bang&quot; and created a polarity, which means the evil and good, minus and plus, zero and one and the TORUS -formed Multiversum. They all are represented in The Number 11, which means TWO DIFFERENT POWERS. You don´t have still to be afraid, just take a look on your swatch or your clock and feel the symmetry of THE TIME : 11.11., 12.12. 13.13. or 21.21., 22.22. etc. It is the Synchronicity of your understanding and flexible time reality and the message of the existence of the  TRUE ANGELS OF THE ALL RELIGIONS OF YOUR PLANET.  Gnuum Wrath Psail Thath Mugr Rah Pioms Mollt Rafd = The Light And Love Goes Together With The Eternal Love and Peace.

PS. Resist the WWIII on your planet, which can start soon.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolon Kokte K’uh and Akhenaten are related to these things. Have you ever wondered, why the ancient cultures have vanished? If you look the South America (Inkas, Mayans), Sumer (Irak and Iran) and Egypt etc. Everything is now fucked up, because the advanced  alien and human civilisations have left the Planet. The Atlantis sinked in the Bermuda Triangle, and that is the reason why the Illuminati controlled scientific community have mapped for instance the Moon better than the Ocean Floor.  Have you ever wondered the Kuiper Belt? Why the asteroids aren´t forming planets as they should be? It´s Because the planet MALDEK destroyed in the past. Illuminati, mainstream scientists and Vatican tell you lies, that the asteroids of the Kuiper Belt are leftovers after the formation of your solar system millions of years ago. Illuminati and Vatican controls your whole planet and keep the important things secret, so that they can manipulate and direct your destiny. Unfortunately the orders comes from much more higher seat. The hierarchy of the Universal Power is multidimensional and eternal and reaches beyond your Space Time Continuum. Unfortunately The Great Architect made a mistake in Your &#8221;Big Bang&#8221; and created a polarity, which means the evil and good, minus and plus, zero and one and the TORUS -formed Multiversum. They all are represented in The Number 11, which means TWO DIFFERENT POWERS. You don´t have still to be afraid, just take a look on your swatch or your clock and feel the symmetry of THE TIME : 11.11., 12.12. 13.13. or 21.21., 22.22. etc. It is the Synchronicity of your understanding and flexible time reality and the message of the existence of the  TRUE ANGELS OF THE ALL RELIGIONS OF YOUR PLANET.  Gnuum Wrath Psail Thath Mugr Rah Pioms Mollt Rafd = The Light And Love Goes Together With The Eternal Love and Peace.</p>
<p>PS. Resist the WWIII on your planet, which can start soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Kirjoittaja: Eija		</title>
		<link>/tiede/paracasin-pidennetyt-kallot-paljastavat-ei-mikaan-tunnettu-eliolaji/#comment-19828</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Eija]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 09:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=650#comment-19828</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Käsittämättömiä juttuja. Etelä-Amerikasta on löydetty näitä kalloja, isoja humanoidien luurankoja ja Ecuadorista tuhansia vuosia vanha musta pyramidi, jonka kärjessä on silmä! Kuka osaa selittää mitä se kaikki tarkoittaa?]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Käsittämättömiä juttuja. Etelä-Amerikasta on löydetty näitä kalloja, isoja humanoidien luurankoja ja Ecuadorista tuhansia vuosia vanha musta pyramidi, jonka kärjessä on silmä! Kuka osaa selittää mitä se kaikki tarkoittaa?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
